Guide to the Brooklyn schools collection 1985.054
Brooklyn Historical Society
- St. Joseph's College for Women, 1967-1968 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  Contains copies of the yearbook Footprints from 1967 and 1968. Donated to the Long Island Historical Society by the Pendleton Fund in memory of James Thorpe Pendleton and Frederick Starr Pendleton, Jr.
- St. Leonard's High School, 1959 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  Contains a copy of the yearbook the Leonardian from 1959.
- St. Michael's Diocesan High School, 1956 (Box 7)
- St. Saviour High School, 1970-1973 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  Contains yearbooks from the years 1970, 1971, 1972, 1973.
- Shore Road Academy, 1929-1930 (Box 7)
- South Brooklyn Female Seminary, 1864 (Box 7)
- Thomas Jefferson High School, 1941 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  Contains a copy of the yearbook Aurora from the year 1941.
- Trinity School of New York, 1859 (Box 7)
- Union Missionary Training Institute, 1915-1916 (Box 7)
- Walt Whitman School, 1916 (Box 7)
- Souvenir of Our Public Schools, Brooklyn N.Y., 1892 (Box 5)
  Published by the New York State Office of Superintendent of Public Instruction. Includes school staff listings, portraits of principals, and photographs of public school buildings in Brooklyn.